avenuek.com 2013-11-18

# Privacy Policy

    Your privacy is very important to us. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect and use information about you when you use the Avenue K website ("Site") and other Avenue K services (together, our "services").

#### Information We Collect

    When you use any of the Avenue K services, we may collect some or all of the following information:
1\. Account Information
    If you register to create an Avenue K account, we will collect your email address and ask you to choose a username. Your username will be publicly displayed and connected to your Avenue K activity. We may also ask you to provide additional personal information such as your full name, billing and/or shipping address, telephone number, credit card information, mailing address, social security number or tax ID, date of birth and/or bank account information. After you have registered, we will collect information about your use of our services. This information can include the date you joined Avenue K, any feedback you have posted, your ratings, items you listed for sale, shop pages, sold item listings, and your comments and postings in community spaces.

2\. Automated Information
     When you visit the Site, we automatically collect information from your browser, including your IP address and data about the pages you visit on the Site. We may also obtain information from third parties, including third party applications you use to login to the site. 
    Like most other online businesses, we may also use cookies, pixels, web beacons, and other automated mechanisms to keep track of user interactions with our site and our advertisements. Through those mechanisms we may collect information such as your mobile device's UDID, your computer's IP address, the type of browser you are using, the websites you visit and the type of things you click on.

#### How We Use Your Information

    Among other things, we use the information we collect to provide and improve our services, to facilitate billing and payment for sale and purchase transactions, to authenticate your identity, to contact you about your account and for internal reporting and planning. We may also use this information to provide you with useful advertising and offers.

#### Third Parties

    Except as specified in this Privacy Policy, Avenue K will not sell, share or disclose information about you to any third party without your express consent.
    We may share the information we collect from you as follows:
    If you are involved in a purchase, sale or other transaction, we will share your information with the other party to facilitate the transaction. For example, we will provide sellers with the email address, shipping address, payment information and/or other information of buyers.
    We may disclose your information in response to a subpoena or compulsory process or if needed to comply with any applicable laws, to prevent imminent harm or financial loss, or to investigate or take action relating to illegal activities, suspected fraud, or violations of Terms of Use found here: [Terms of Use](http://www.avenuek.com/terms-of-use). We also reserve the right to provide your information to a third party if we believe such disclosure is necessary to prevent harm or liability to us, to our other users or to a third party.
    We may share information with affiliated businesses that offer promotions or sell items or services to you through the Site or other services. We may also provide services or sell products jointly with affiliated businesses. 
    We may share your information any third party who is helping us provide the services (e.g., credit card and other payment processors). 
    We may transfer information about you as part of due diligence or an actual or potential sale or merger of our business. 
    We may also use third party analytics services, such as Google Analytics. These services may use technical means such as cookies (which are text files placed on your computer) to collect information that will be transmitted to and stored on their servers. The analytics services use this information to evaluate your use of our services, compile reports on website activity and provide us with other services. They may also transfer information to third parties if they are legally required to do so or where such third parties process information on their behalf. You can refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser but if you do so, you will not be able to use the full functionality of the Site. By using the Site, you consent to our analytics providers' processing your data as described above.

#### Posted Content

    If you post anything in a public area of the site, your information can be read, collected and used by others. Your posts may remain on the Site even after your account is closed. We advise against posting personal information in publicly visible areas of the site.

#### Security

    We take the security of your personal information very seriously. We ask that you also take responsibility for protecting your password safeguarding your account against unauthorized access. While we strive to protect the personal information you give us, we cannot guarantee its absolute security because no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is entirely secure. 

#### Retention of Your Information

    We may keep your information as long as you have an account with us or as needed to provide you with the services. We may also retain and use your information after you close your account if we believe it is necessary or beneficial for legal compliance or to resolve disputes, operate our business or enforce our agreements.

#### Modifications and Changes

    We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time. We will let you know of any changes by posting a notice on the Site and/or by notifying you via email. Any changes will take place at the time of posting and will not apply retroactively without your consent, unless they are required by law to do so.

#### Location of Your Information

    Your information may be transferred to and maintained on servers outside your country. We process and store information in the United States and your use of our services constitutes your consent to and understanding of this transfer and processing.

#### California Residents

    Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, users who are California residents are entitled to request and receive once a year, free of charge, a notice from us describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared, the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, and their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to 3415 Sepulveda Boulevard, Suite 340, Los Angeles, CA 90034. In your request, please specify that you want a "California Privacy Rights Notice." Please allow at least thirty days for a response.

#### Contact Us

    To contact Avenue K about anything in our Privacy Policy, including any questions or suggestions, please send an email to 3415 Sepulveda Boulevard, Suite 340, Los Angeles, CA 90034; telephone: 1-877-270-4777.

Posted July 1, 2013

x

### select your country

Note: Currency conversion is for reference only.

Orders will be processed in $ US Dollars.
